<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Composite//EN" "technicalContent/dtd/ditabase.dtd" [
]>

<concept id = "i720813">
<title>About The Sample <b><b>ePublisher</b> Express</b> Trial Source Documents</title>
<shortdesc>These <b>WebWorks</b> sample source documents contain predetermined paragraph and character styles,
 marker types, conditions, variables, and cross-reference definitions that you can use to explore 
 <b>ePublisher</b> capabilities and generate output.</shortdesc>
<conbody>
    <p>For example, the <b>WebWorks</b> sample source documents contain sample paragraph styles, such as
	Heading 1, Heading 2, Title, and Body paragraph styles, and sample character styles, such as Bold
	and Emphasis, that are common in most source documents. These are not meant to show you all of <b>ePublisher's</b>
	capabilities, but to give you enough information to make an informed decision.</p>
    <p>The sample source documents provided were created to be used in the following ways:
      <ol>
	   <li>
	   <p>You can follow the instructions in the <b><b>ePublisher</b> Express</b> Trial Guide (located on the start
	   page.) The <b><b>ePublisher</b> Express</b> Trial guide will give you a good idea of how to use the <b>ePublisher</b>
	   interface and it will explain the design of our HTML5 document set. It then takes you through 
	   some tasks using the <b>ePublisher</b> system. During those task, you will use the instructions in this
	   source document to edit the source before generating the HTML5 document set. Once generated, you
	   will verify your work in the document set then return to the guide for the next task.</p>
	   </li>
       <li>
	   <p>In the <b>My Edits</b> group, you can replace the existing content in the sample documents with some
	   of your content, apply the provided paragraph and character styles and marker types available in
	   the sample source documents to your content, and then generate and review output.</p>
	   </li>
	  </ol>
    </p>
	<p>The instructions provided in the sample source documents to help you explore <b>ePublisher</b> assume 
	that you already know how to work within your preferred authoring tool and file format. The 
	documents give hints to help you along, but if at any point you feel you need a little more 
	instruction, or if you have a question specific to your work flow just click on the “Contact Us” 
	link in Next Steps.</p>
	<p>The source documents are meant to give you live examples of the <b>ePublisher</b> work flow. How you 
	would use the system on a day to day basis. If you find any errors in the document, try making 
	edits and then generating a new correct HTML5 document set. That is the closest we can get you to a
	real-world example, so you can have enough information to make an informed decision.</p>
</conbody>
</concept>
