<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Composite//EN" "technicalContent/dtd/ditabase.dtd" [
]>



<concept id = "i720844"><title>Adding Functional Elements to Online
Content Using ePublisher</title>
  <shortdesc>When delivering your content through an online medium, there are many online features that
  you can take advantage of to increase the satisfaction of your audience.</shortdesc>
  <conbody>
    <p>For example, online features such as "Expand/Collapse" sections, "Related Topics" links, and "mini 
	Table of Contents" (great for mobile outputs.) <b>ePublisher</b> makes it easy to incorporate these 
	features into your output by simply marking sections of your source documents with the appropriate
	paragraph, character styles, marker types or output class. You do not need to write code for any of
	these features.</p>
    <p>The following sections explain how to implement these features using the <b>ePublisher</b> system. You
	will use the proper paragraph or character styles, marker types or output class in the sample 
	source documents to implement the following online features:
      <ul>
        <li><xref href="../ExpandCollapseSections/expandcollapse_sections.xml#i720762"
                        >"Expand/Collapse Sections"</xref>
	    </li>
        <li><xref href="../RelatedTopics/related_topics_links.xml#i720834"
                        >"Related Topics Links"</xref>
	    </li>
        <li><xref href="../ContextSensitiveTopics/context_sensitive_help_topics.xml#i721201"
                        >"Context-Sensitive Help Topics"</xref>
	    </li>
        <li><xref href="../MiniTOCsForMobileDevices/mini_tocs_for_mobile_devices.xml#i720932"
                        >"Mini Table of Content for Mobile Devices"</xref>
	    </li>
      </ul>
    </p>
    <p>Then in the “My Edits” section, you will see examples of how to incorporate different types 
	of media assets using your authoring tools native insert ability, or by using conditional text. 
	When installing <b>ePublisher</b>, we add a menu to give you the ability to use markers and conditional 
	text if your authoring tool does not have that ability.</p>
  </conbody>
</concept>
