<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE reference PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Composite//EN" "technicalContent/dtd/ditabase.dtd" [
]>


<reference id = "i721408">
<title>Paragraph Formats</title>
<shortdesc>Paragraph formats apply to entire paragraphs of text.</shortdesc>
<refbody>
<section id = "i721398">
  <p>Use paragraph formats if you want to apply a certain formatting to a particular
   section of your content.
   <dl>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>Body</dt>
	   <dd>All content that serves as the body of this document uses the Body paragraph
	   format. For example, any text that is not part of a table, numbered or bulleted
	   list should use the Body paragraph format.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
	 <dlentry>
	   <dt>Bullet, Bullet2</dt>
	   <dd>The Bullet formats allow you to create unordered lists. The Bullet formats
	   provide you with a level of indentation that matches exactly with your Body
	   paragraph format. The Bullet2 format provides you with one level of indentation
	   from the Body paragraph format.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
	 <dlentry>
	   <dt>Chapter Title</dt>
	   <dd>The Chapter Title paragraph format allows you to identify new chapters in
	   your document. This format uses autonumbering to append chapter numbers to your
	   headings.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>ExpandCollapse</dt>
       <dd>The ExpandCollapse format creates links that display or hide content in an
	   expand/collapse section in generated output. Apply this format to any text
	   that you want to serve as a link for an expand/collapse section.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>GlossDef</dt>
       <dd>The GlossDef format should be applied to the glossary definition for 
	   glossary terms.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>GlossTerm</dt>
       <dd>Content with the GlossTerm format should always precede the GlossDef
	   format.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>Heading1, Heading 2, and Heading 3</dt>
       <dd>Heading formats can be used to label titles for major sections in source 
	   documents. Each heading format differs in font size and font weight.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>Indent1, Indent2</dt>
       <dd>The Indent formats should be used when you want to apply a greater level of 
	   indentation to your Body format. Use Indent1 if you want to indent your content
	   one level in from the Body format. Use Indent2 if you want to indent your 
	   content two levels in from the Body format.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>Number, Number1</dt>
       <dd>The Number formats allow you to create ordered lists. The first item in 
	   your list should use the Number1 format, and the content following the first
	   item should use the Number format.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>ProcedureTitle</dt>
       <dd>The ProcedureTitle format should be used for procedure introductory statements.
	   Apply this format to any text that introduces the procedure. This format does not
	   create expand/collapse sections that display or hide steps in a procedure. If you
	   want to create procedure introductory statements that display or hide steps in a 
	   procedure, use the ExpandCollapse paragraph format.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
     <dlentry>
	   <dt>RelatedTopic</dt>
       <dd>The RelatedTopic format creates related topics links in generated output. Apply
	   this format to a list of cross-references that you want to display as links in your
	   generated output.</dd>
	 </dlentry>
    </dl>
  </p>
</section>
</refbody>
</reference>
