<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Composite//EN" "technicalContent/dtd/ditabase.dtd" [
]>

<concept id = "i721365">
<title>Creating Context-Sensitive Help Topics</title>
<prolog>
  <metadata>
    <othermeta name="TopicAlias" content="IDH_CreatingContextSensitiveHelpTopics"/>
  </metadata>
</prolog>
<shortdesc>Context-sensitive help topics provide users with immediate assistance without requiring them
 to leave the context in which they are working.</shortdesc>
  <conbody>
    <p>They help answer questions like "What is this?" and "Why would I use this?", and they provide
	information for a particular object and its context. Many applications support context-sensitive help
	by allowing a user to click on a Help button on an application window. When the user clicks on the Help
	button, a context-sensitive help topic related to the application window the user is viewing displays.
	</p>
    <p>For example, within an application, you might see the following window:
	  <fig frame="all" id="i721291"><image href="Images/ContextSensitiveHelp1.png"/></fig>
	</p>
    <p>If the user clicks on the Help button, then the context-sensitive help topic associated with the
	window displays.
	</p>
    <p>ePublisher allows you to create context-sensitive help topics through the use of TopicAlias markers
	and specific Universal Resource Locator (URL). The content creator inserts a TopicAlias marker in each
	context-sensitive help topic they create. With TopicAlias markers, ePublisher allows for a specify the
	URL address in the text of the marker. Applications use the specific URL to determine which topic to
	display when users click on the Help button on an application window.
	</p>
    <p>In this topic, the <codeph>&lt;prolog&gt;</codeph> has 
	<codeph>&lt;othermeta&gt;</codeph> formatted as a TopicAlias marker that
	ePublisher can identify.
	</p>
    <p>The topic ID specified in the TopicAlias marker is: IDH_CreatingContextSensitiveHelpTopics.</p>
    <p>The Stationery Designer assigned the appropriate context-sensitive behavior to the TopicAlias marker
	type in the sample ePublisher Express Trial stationery. You can see this TopicAlias marker through the
	reporting feature of ePublisher. Every time you have ePublisher generate output, it creates reports so
	you can easily manage aspects of your publishing workflow. If you take a look at the reports window (scroll
	down to the bottom of the Output Explorer window) You can see, we give you two types of reports:
	<fig frame="all" id="i721297"><image href="Images/ReportsWindow.png"/></fig>
	</p>
    <p>The first section (in green) is for in-product reporting. Clicking these links will display the output
	in the ePublisher Working Area, and give you access to helpful links. The second section (in yellow) is the same report
	with the same information. It is just formatted in HTML to make the information print friendly. It will
	contain the same helpful links.
	</p>
    <p>To view the TopicAlias marker, use the “Topics Report” in the printable section.</p>
    <p>Clicking on the Topics Report will open a new browser window. The description section lists the actual
	path for the topic. This path is what the developers use to trigger the help topic when a user would click
	on a “?” or some other icon your company has chosen to represent help guides. You can experience that
	functionality by clicking on the word “Output” under the Links section.
	</p>
    <p>Using ePublisher to generate your TopicAlias markers is the simplest way to manage context-sensitive
	help in your product. As long as the name of the marker never changes, the path generated by ePublisher will
	never change, giving you peace of mind when it comes to your context-sensitive help.
	</p>
  </conbody>
</concept>
