<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Composite//EN" "technicalContent/dtd/ditabase.dtd" [
]>


<concept id = "i920767">
<title>Inserting a Video in DITA With The <codeph>&lt;xref href&gt;</codeph> Element</title>
<shortdesc>In this section, the process on how to insert a video into DITA using
the <codeph>&lt;href&gt;</codeph>element will be included below. Use this space to 
link to any videos you would like to see in ePublisher's HTML5 document set.</shortdesc>
<conbody>
  <p>The information for linking in DITA can be found on the OASIS website here:
  <xref href="https://docs.oasis-open.org/dita/v1.0/langspec/link.html">
  <b>TO OASIS</b></xref></p>
  <p><b>link</b></p>
  <p>The <codeph>&lt;link&gt;</codeph> element defines a relationship to another 
  topic. Links represent the types and roles of topics in a web of information, and
  therefore represent navigational links within that web. Links are typically sorted
  on output based on their attributes. The optional container elements for link
  (<codeph>&lt;linkgroup&gt;</codeph> and <codeph>&lt;linklist&gt;</codeph>) allow 
  authors to define groups with common attributes, or to preserve the authored 
  sequence of links on output.</p>
  <p><b><codeph>&lt;xref href&gt;</codeph></b></p>
  <p>Description</p>
  <p>A hyperlink to an external Web page (URL) or other non-DITA resource, or to 
  another DITA topic in the same file or in another file. The format attribute 
  identifies the format of the target. Non-DITA targets use standard URL syntax. 
  DITA topics are targetted as follows:</p>
  <p><codeph>Target elsewhere in the same file: href="#topicid"</codeph></p>
  <p><codeph>First topic in different file: href="filename.dita"</codeph></p>
  <p><codeph>Specific topic in different file: href="filename.dita#topicid"</codeph></p>
  <p>Below is a link to a youtube video</p>
  <p><xref href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D4QoQWboM-U">
  Click for video</xref></p>
  <p>Inserting a video this way will open another browser. The next section 
  will discusses how to embed a video</p>
</conbody>
</concept>
